Yeah, AJ, congratulations. Can you, can
you tell me the origin of your nickname?
One more time.
Can you, can you tell me the origin of
your nickname?
The origin of my nickname, Mr. Give Me
That. Hey, Mr. Give Me That.
So, it was it Mr. Give Me That
originated in high school. In high
school, you know, I was a ball-hawking
cornerback. I played corner in high
school and, you know, I was ball-hawking
and one day my cousin, he text me,
"Let's get another interception." Cuz
the next game was coming up, Mr. Give Me
That. So, my cousin, he he gave me this
name, Mr. Give Me That. Yes, sir. My
cousin.
Jake.
Hey, AJ. So, it seems like you've really
kind of had to embrace the grind to get
here. You know, New Mexico, Houston,
LSU. You've kind of made all-conference
everywhere. You're a four-year special
teams player. Like,
what's How much does that mean to you to
just make sure you are working as hard
as possible to get where you're at?
I mean, it means a lot, you know. Um
just consistently just working, you
know, I even canceled some visits and
and some some some Zoom calls just to go
work out. So, you know, I fell in love
with it, you know. I fell in love with
field work. Like, field work, you know,
is where I release everything that I've
been dealing with and when I when when I
challenge myself, you know, and in the
weight room as well. But, you know, I
just fell in love with the work and
you know, I'm ready to just um
show the league what I got, you know.
Every every stop that I've been to New
Mexico to Houston to to LSU, like
it was all it was all a learning
experience. So, when I get to the next
level, I just take everything I learned
from wherever I've been and take it to
wherever I'm going and, you know, that's
what helped me out the most. The the the
the more experience and just the the
things that I learned down the way.
Mara, go ahead.
Looks like an incredible celebration and
gathering that you have there tonight.
Can you just take us through that phone
call, the reaction, learning that it's
the call I was waiting on it, man. I was
waiting on it, man. I was waiting on
this phone call forever, man. It felt
like I waited forever and and
and all I needed to see was I N N and I
knew I knew who was calling me. I knew
who was calling. You know,
been on me. I kind of had a little
feeling that I was going to end up being
a Colt and you know, that was a
wonderful feeling. That was a great
feeling. And soon as I seen the phone
call, you know,
I kind of left the the living room area
where all the people was and I kind of
went there by myself and you know, I was
just getting on my knees ready to pray
and uh you know, the phone start
ringing. So,
I had already prayed before this and I
know God make no mistake. So,
the place that I landed now is the place
that that that really wanted me and that
they that I know that they're going to
try their best and they're going to do
their best to use me and to just, you
know, coach me and to just just teach me
the teach me the scheme and everything,
you know. I'm just glad to be a Colt.
So, when I seen that phone call, you
know, I was very excited.
James, go ahead.
AJ, congratulations. I can see the smile
from here to Indianapolis. But, um Let's
do it.
>> [laughter]
>> Let's do it, man. Let's do it, man.
>> How much do you think your experience
playing in so many different defenses in
college can help you transition into the
NFL?
Man, it helps a lot, you know. Just
hearing different terminology, you know.
And I think that's the biggest thing.
Hearing the terminology and just, you
know, kind of figuring kind of figuring
out each defense. Okay, this is cover
four. Okay, this is cover three. The
cover three team,
I'm going to get all the routes that
could be cover three in in this scheme.
So, when I transfer, I'm now I'm in a
big quarter I'm in a big quarters team.
So, okay, we're going to get all the
routes that could beat us in quarters
and then just when I get to the league,
whatever scheme I'm in, you know, I can
Okay, I know it's going to be me in
three. I know it's going to be me in
quarters. I know it's going to be me in
two. Just because of I've been in
scheme-heavy defenses like
this scheme is cover two. This scheme is
cover three. We're going to master the
cover three and then play spot drop. So,
I say it play a major role in just my my
intelligence and what I know just on the
field and pre-snap and what I can
diagnose. So, that lead my instincts to
kick in.
Joel, go ahead.
What do you think the toughest thing you
had to overcome is on your way to the
NFL?
>> [snorts]
>> I just say um discipline, you know. You
know, discipline is
is is such a hard thing to just to just
maintain, you know.
And and once you just just focus and
lock in, like, discipline was the main
thing that I had to overcome. Like, it
was plenty nights I wanted to do other
things and it was plenty nights that I
could have did other things. But, you
know, the love of the game was just
always there for me and the game that I
knew how to play
really well, you know, was just always
there for me. So, I just say discipline
and and and and just staying focused,
you know, staying focused on the main
thing and not and not getting distracted
just because of, you know, where I grew
up from and and where I'm from, you
know, just not getting distracted and
just staying on. I knew if I stayed on,
I was going to do it. So, God God God
led me and I stayed on and God was right
there with me. So, I'm here right now.
Yeah, I hate that. We'll do just a few
more.
>> I'm here right now,
man.
Jake, go ahead.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
>> Before I get into that, AJ, you've held
up that shirt a couple times. What
What's that mean to you?
Yes, sir.
Man, it means a lot, you know. Um
that just shows just other people just
where I'm from, like
it it could go down in many directions,
you know. Just just me being able to
focus and just football being an outlet
for me, like
the person that I'm holding up right now
is was a really close friend of mine and
unfortunately, he passed away and um
you know, I get kind of
emotional, you know, when I speak on
those things. But,
you know,
and and and that's just an example of a
person that did not have football as an
outlet for them. You know, they never
found the love of the game for the for
themselves and you know, and and and
that's one of the routes that you go
down for where I'm from. But, you know,
he's a really close friend of mine and
he always wanted me to pursue the the
dream of football. And guess what, Trey?
We're here right now. So, I just want to
say I love him and I thank him for just
watching over me and just getting me
here and and he just showed me what what
what not to do. And you know, I just
can't thank him enough. I love him to
death.
Okay. That's good to hear. And not to
take too much of a left turn. But,
you've got a ton of snaps, you know, up
high in the box. The Colts' biggest
opening, you know, they they lost their
starter, their starting box safety this
offseason. What's your comfort level
there if if that's where you're asked to
fill in?
Yeah, I'm ready to do it, man. I didn't
play in a box my whole college journey.
I didn't play up high my whole college
journey. Like, if you if you had a snap
count, I know it's going to be 50/50.
Like,
I didn't I didn't play up
high. I didn't play down low. So, I'm
very comfortable with the tackle pull.
I'm shooting that gap and and if he pass
block, I'm ready to read the eyes of the
quarterback or I'm ready to guard
whoever I got to guard.
You just know you're going to get a dog
out of me, man. I'm going to be a guy
that's going to stay after practice and
I'm going to be a guy that's going to
stay on the field. And I'm also going to
be in a guy that's going to stay in the
film room. So, any little tricks that
whatever team come with, I'm ready to
stop them and I'm ready to get the ball
back to our offense. Let's go score
points. Let's do it. Let's do it.
>> [laughter]
>> Let's do it.
We'll go [clears throat] with Trey.
>> Let's do it, man.
You'll be our last question.
Hey, AJ. Congrats.
Um when did you make the switch? You
said high school cornerback to safety.
And for those that haven't seen you
play, how would you describe your
playing style?
I made the switch right after my my
senior in high school. So, I made the
switch my freshman year, you know, and I
ended up being a freshman All-American.
I had like a a 24-tackle game and I also
had a uh my second play in just
starting. I was third string up until
the third game up until the third game
of my college my freshman year. And
you know, my second play in, I caught an
interception. So, um
you know, I feel like I
the way that I prepare and the way that
I just pray, you know, God got me
through everything, you know. And even
when I was third string, I was still one
of the teammates that was going to tell
whoever it was in the game their job and
I was going to try to help them out as
best as best as possible and I was going
to give them all the game that I knew.
So,
I just say um
you know, just me being myself, you
know. Um
it just means a lot. And and I should
Can you repeat that question? Cuz I kind
of went
You know, I'm just I'm just glad right
now. Can you repeat your question one
more time?
Yeah, I was just asking stylistically,
how would you describe your own playing
style?
>> Okay. Okay. Myself, I'm very
instinctive. I'm very
I'm a very instinctive player, you know,
and I use my instincts and my film study
to lead my game, you know. And
I'm very physical and aggressive, you
know. I
It's like when teams come to my side or
come to my side, it's like I'm going to
stop
you trying me and I want to make you pay
every single time. Like I said,
what type of player I am. So, my film
study and my instincts lead my
I play with a lot of aggression.
I need my homie.
James, go ahead.
Uh the only thing I really had to ask AJ
was how do you spell Trey's last name if
you don't mind? Sounds like he's a big
part of your journey. We just want to
make sure we get that correct when we
write our stories.
B O W I E
Okay. Thank you and and congrats again.
And it seems like you're excited and you
should be.
Congrats, AJ. Hey, I'll be
THERE. LET'S DO IT. Y'ALL GOT A DOG,
MAN. Y'all got a dog.